Inventory of the Addition to the Papers of Daniel J. Meador 1973-1995
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
Inventory of the Addition to the Papers of Daniel J. Meador 1973-1995
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 82-3c
This collection consists of 3 boxes.
This addition to the Meador papers consists of committee files and student face books.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Professor Meador donated these papers to the law school in 1995.
Contents List
- Comparative Law Professor Search Committee 1989 (Box 1)
- Curriculum Revision 1990 (Box 1)
- Faculty Study Group 1973 (Box 1)
- Interview for oral history project. UVA 1995 (Box 1)
- Handicapped Students Committee 1989-1990 (Box 1)
- Law School Committee-Retiring Faculty 1988 (Box 1)
- Law School Graduate Program 1985-1987 (Box 1)
- Moot Court 1987-1993 (Box 1)
- Law School Miscellaneous Papers 1960-72, 1984-94, 11 folders (Box 2-3)
- Photographs
  - Class of 1987. Face Book--Graduate Students
  - Class of 1988. Face Book--Transfer Students
  - Class of 1990. Face Book
  - Class of 1991. Face Book--Graduate and Transfer Students
  - Class of 1992. Face Book
  - Class of 1993. Face Book
  - Class of 1993. Face Book
  - Class of 1994. Face Book
  - Class of 1995. Face Book